Guide to the Abe Burrows papers, 1904-1993
The New York Public Library. Billy Rose Theatre Division.
- Series III: Production Files, 1912-1992; 588728; 54 boxes
  - Sub-series 1 - By Title, 1950-1981; 588729; 45 boxes
    - Cactus Flower by Abe Burrows, 589156
      - Script, clean, n.d.; 589160; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Script, mostly clean, n.d.; 589161; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Script, mostly clean, n.d.; 589162; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Script with revisions, n.d.; 589163; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Script with revisions and staging notes written in, 589164; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - "First Draft,", 1965 July 14; 589165; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Script and revisions, 589166; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Script and revisions, 589167; 2 folders (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
      - Scenes and revisions, 1965 Sept 22-Oct 20; 589168; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Script synopsis, n.d.; 589169; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Scripts in French, 1964 Sept-Nov; 589170; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Early background material, 589171; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Notes to actors, 1965-1968; 589172; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Casting and contact sheets, 1965; 589173; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Contracts, 1964-1966; 589174; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Contracts: minimum basic production, 1964-1966; 589175; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Contracts: joint venture agreement, 1965-1966; 589176; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Contracts: Melpomene Productions and David Merrick, 1965-1966; 589177; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Contracts: Beresford Productions and Samuel French, 1967; 589178; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Contracts: director's agreement with David Merrick, 1969; 589179; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Copyright: certificates and correspondence, 1966-1984; 589180; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Motion picture sales, 1965-1973; 589181; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Contracts: Beresford Productions with Columbia Pictures, 1973-1974; 589182; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Legal correspondence, 1965-1968; 589183; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - General correspondence, 1965-1977; 589184; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Business correspondence, 1965-1975; 589185; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Financial statements, 1965-1970; 589186; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Financial statements, joint ventures, 1966-1970; 589187; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Royalty statements, 1968-1972; 589188; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Royalty statements, 1979-1981; 589189; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Programs, including souvenir program, and opening night list, 1964-1968; 589190; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Clippings and publicity, 1965-1968; 589191; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Photographs of Lauren Bacall and Abe Burrows, 589192; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, schedules and financial papers on national tour, 1967; 589193; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Programs, publicity and clippings on national tour, 1967; 589194; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, schedule, financial papers and publicity for London production, 1966-1968; 589195; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Business correspondence and statements for film, 1970-1972; 589196; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Film reviews, 1969; 589197; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence and contracts on possible musical adaptation, 1982-1983; 589198; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - O.K. Crackerby! by Abe Burrows, 589199
      - Story presentation, My Man St. John, by C. Amory for television series, n.d.; 589200; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Script, My Man St. John, by Abe Burrows for television series, n.d.; 589201; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Story line, drafts for My Man St. John (television), n.d.; 589202; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Script, second episode of television series, 589203; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Possible story lines, scripts, correspondence and memos for television series, 1965 Jan-July; 589204; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous drafts of scripts, 1964-1965; 589205; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Handwritten notes, 589206; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Theme music, lyrics, 1965; 589207; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Cast lists, photographs and set layout, 1964 and n.d; 589208; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Contracts, 1964-1965; 589209; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Agreements, contracts, writers' reports, 1964-1970; 589210; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1966; 589211; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence with William Morris Agency, Inc., 1965; 589212; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Royalty statements, 1966-1970; 589213; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Clippings, 1964-1965; 589214; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Holly Golightly music and lyrics by Robert Merrill, book by Abe Burrows, based on the novel Breakfast at Tiffany's by Truman Capote, 589215
      - Screenplay of Breakfast at Tiffany's, n.d.; 589216; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Play script with revisions and song lyrics, 1966 Sept-Nov; 589217; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Play script with revisions, lyrics and music cues, 1966 Oct-Nov; 589218; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Play script with revisions and song lyrics, 589219; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Scenes and revisions, 1966 Aug-Sept and n.d; 589220; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Scenes and revisions, 1966 Sept and n.d; 589221; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Scenes and revisions, 1966 Sept-Oct; 589222; 2 folders (Box 55, Folder 7-8)
      - Scenes and revisions, mostly n.d.; 589223; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Scenes, notes and revisions, 1966 June-Nov; 589224; 3 folders (Box 56, Folder 2-4)
      - Running order and notes on changes, 1966 May 6-Sept 8; 589225; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Edward Albee rewrites and letter, 589226; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 6)
        Includes letter to Burrows from Ed O'Connor.
      - Correspondence and notes on casting, 1966 Feb-Aug; 589227; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Contact sheet and travel call, 1966 Oct 4; 589228; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Set designs by Oliver Smith, 1966; 589229; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Set of contracts, 1966; 589230; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Contracts, "original,", 1966 Aug-Sept; 589231; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Contracts: director's agreement, 1966; 589232; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Contracts: Dramatists Guild, 1966-1984; 589233; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Contracts with Nunnally Johnson, 1966; 589234; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Contracts with Michael Kidd, 1966; 589235; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Contracts: joint venture, 1966; 589236; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Contracts with Paramount Pictures, 1966; 589237; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Contracts, general, 1966-1967; 589238; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1966; 589239; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Business correspondence, 1966 Sept-1967 Jan; 589240; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Programs, n.d.; 589241; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Clippings and publicity, 1966; 589242; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Photographs, 1966; 589243; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Forty Carats by Jay Allen, 589244
      - Clean typescript, n.d.; 589245; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Clean typescript, n.d.; 589246; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Clean typescript with mimeographed pages of new script, n.d.; 589247; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Script notes, 1969 Jan 13-1970 July 1; 589248; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - Contact sheets and bows, 589249; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - Contracts, (set of basic documents), 1967-1969; 589250; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Contracts, general, 1968-1971; 589251; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Contracts, miscellaneous, 1968-1970; 589252; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Contracts: author's agreement with Jay Allen, 1968-1969; 589253; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Contracts: director's agreement, 1968 Sept; 589254; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Contracts: joint venture agreement, 1968-1969; 589255; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Contracts: joint venture agreement, 1969-1972; 589256; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Contracts: arbitration proceedings, Beresford Productions vs. David Merrick, 1971-1972; 589257; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1968-1972; 589258; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Business correspondence, 1968-1971; 589259; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - Stock royalties, 1970-1980; 589260; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Programs with Julie Harris and opening night list, 1968 Nov-Dec; 589261; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Programs with Zsa Zsa Gabor, 1970 July; 589262; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - Original French production: program and photographs, 589263; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Clippings, 1968-1970; 589264; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Clippings, national tour, 1969-1970; 589265; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 16)
      - Papers relating to motion picture, 1972; 589266; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - The Flip Side play by Hugh and Margaret Williams, screenplay by Abe Burrows, 589267
      - Play script, clean, n.d.; 589268; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Screenplay, "First Draft," clean, 1968 May 15; 589269; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Screenplay, "First Draft," mostly clean carbon, 1968 Sept 18; 589270; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Screenplay, "2nd draft," clean, 589271; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Draft with revisions, 1968 July-Aug; 589272; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Draft with revisions, incomplete, 1968 July-Aug; 589273; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Draft with revisions, miscellaneous dates, 1968 July-Sept; 589274; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Drafts, partial, carbon with some revisions, 1968 Sept 18; 589275; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Drafts, carbon, 1969 Jan; 589276; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Odd script pages, revised, some handwritten, 589277; 4 folders (Box 60, Folder 3-6)
      - Rough layout and notes, 1968 June; 589278; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Contracts and legal correspondence, 1968-1969; 589279; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1968-1969; 589280; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Four on a Garden adapted by Abe Burrows from French play by Pierre Barillet and Jean Pierre Gredy, 589281
      - Script, clean (English translation of French play), n.d.; 589282; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Script, with revisions (Burrows' adaptation), 1971 Jan-1972 Oct; 589283; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Script, clean carbon (four playlets), n.d.; 589284; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Script with revisions, including handwritten pages, 1969 Aug-1970 Sept; 589285; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Script with revisions, 1970 Apr-July; 589286; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Script with revisions, 1970 Sept-1972 Oct; 589287; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Notes on costumes, n.d.; 589288; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Set designs by Oliver Smith, 1970; 589289; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Contact sheet for cast, n.d.; 589290; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Contracts, 1969-1970; 589291; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Contracts with authors of French original, 1969-1970; 589292; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Contracts: director's agreement with David Merrick, 1970; 589293; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Contracts: joint venture, 1970 May 15; 589294; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Contracts: minimum basic production, 1970; 589295; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - Legal correspondence, 1969-1972; 589296; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Legal correspondence on The Swingers, 1972 May 13-15; 589297; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1969-1971; 589298; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Business correspondence, 1969-1973; 589299; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Stock royalties, 1979-1981; 589300; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Program, 1971 Feb.; 589301; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Program and photograph from French production, 1969 May 1 and n.d; 589302; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Clippings, 1970-1971; 589303; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Photographs: Abe Burrows and Carol Channing, 589304; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - No Hard Feelings by Sam Bobrick and Ron Clark, 589305
      - Script, carbon, with a few revisions, 1972 Sept-Oct; 589306; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Script with revisions, 1973 Feb-Mar; 589307; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Scenes and revisions, 1972 Oct-Dec; 589308; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - Sets and props, 589309; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Schedules, 1973; 589310; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - Casting, 1972 Oct-Dec; 589311; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 15)
      - Contact sheets, 1972; 589312; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 16)
      - Contracts (one set), 1972 Sept-Nov; 589313; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 17)
      - Contracts: agreement with authors on subsidiary rights, 1972 Sept-Nov; 589314; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 18)
        Also called Mrs. Bartlett Is Engaged.
      - Contracts: director's agreement, 1972 Sept-Oct; 589315; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 19)
      - Contracts: joint venture agreement, 1972 Sept 21; 589316; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 20)
      - Contracts: minimum basic production, 1972 Feb-Oct; 589317; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 21)
      - Contracts, miscellaneous, 1972-1977; 589318; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1973; 589319; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 23)
      - Program, 1973 Apr 8; 589320; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 24)
      - Clippings, 1973; 589321; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Good News music by Ray Henderson, book by Laurence Schwab and B. G. DeSylva, lyrics by B. G. DeSylva and Lew Brown, adapted and directed by Abe Burrows, 589322
      - Published script with a few pencil notations, 1959; 589323; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Script, clean, 1973 Nov 1; 589324; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Script, carbon, with some revisions, 1973 Nov 9; 589325; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Script, photocopied, called "revised production script,", 1974 Sept 5; 589326; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Notes and jokes, 1972-1973; 589327; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Sheet music, published, 1926-1959; 589328; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Contact sheets, schedule, Burrows' bio, 1973 Nov; 589329; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Contracts (one set), 1973-1974; 589330; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Contracts: director's agreement, 1973; 589331; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Contracts: joint venture agreement, 1973; 589332; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Contracts, minimum basic production, 1973-1974; 589333; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Contracts, miscellaneous, 1973; 589334; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - "Incidental papers,", 1973-1991; 589335; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Legal correspondence, 1973-1978; 589336; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Two letters from producer, Harry Rigby, 1974 Sept 17-Dec 16; 589337; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1974; 589338; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Business correspondence, 1973-1978; 589339; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Programs, 1973-1974; 589340; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Clippings, 1974-1975; 589341; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Photographs, n.d.; 589342; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Hellzapoppin' adapted by Abe Burrows from original book by Ole Olsen and Chic Johnson, 589343
      - Casting, 1976; 589344; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Sheet music, 1976; 589345; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Contracts, 1976-1977; 589346; 2 folders (Box 64, Folder 12-13)
      - Legal correspondence and contracts, 1976-1977; 589347; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - Beresford Productions vs. Alexander Cohen, 1976-1977; 589348; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - Memoranda, 1977; 589349; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, 1976 and n.d; 589350; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - Clippings, 1976-1977; 589351; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Forty-Second Street book by Michael Stewart and Mark Bramble, songs by Harry Warren and Al Dubin, based on the novel by Bradford Ropes, 589352
      - Script, photocopied, mostly clean, with lyrics, n.d.; 589353; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 1)
        Burrows' name is written on title page. He was brought in as director in 1981.
      - Contact lists, 1980-1981; 589354; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Cancelled checks to Beresford Productions, 1981; 589355; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Programs, 1980-1981; 589356; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - [FAKE UNITTITLE], 589357
  - Sub-series 2 - Not Produced, 1912-1981 and n.d; 589358; 5 boxes
    This sub-series includes various materials: scripts, drafts, notes, memos, research, songs, designs, contracts, correspondence and clippings for projects that were ultimately not produced with Burrows' involvement, if ever.
    Chronological
    - Top Ten by Abe Burrows, 589359
      - "First Draft,", 1956 Mar 12-14; 589360; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Script pages, outlines, notes and revisions, 1953 Sept 17-1956 Feb 22; 589361; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Songs, 1953 Nov 11 and n.d; 589362; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1954-1956; 589363; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Clippings and miscellaneous, 1954; 589364; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Countess to Boot book by Jack Iams, musical version by Jack Lawrence and Don Walker, 589365
      - Synopsis, notes and drafts, 1955 May 3 and n.d; 589366; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence and casting ideas, 1955; 589367; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - You Know Me, Al, book by Ring Lardner, television adaptation by Abe Burrows, 589368
      - Screenplay, clean, 1957 Nov 25; 589369; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous draft pages, 1957 Sept 25; 589370; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - "First draft," incomplete, 1957 Sept 13-25; 589371; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - "Concept approach" and notes, 1957 June 6 and n.d; 589372; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence and memos, 1957-1981; 589373; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - Clipping, 1957 Sept 25; 589374; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Fun On Broadway, a proposed one hour television special by Abe Burrows for NBC featuring songs from musical comedies, 589375
      - Proposal, notes and correspondence, 1962; 589376; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Mary Martin Special, a proposed television special for NBC, with treatment by Abe Burrows, 589377
      - Ideas, notes and outline treatment, 1962; 589378; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 19)
      - Sheet music, 1922-1959; 589379; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence with William Morris on contracts, 1962; 589380; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, 1962; 589381; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Love and Taxes, a proposed movie adapted from Janus a play by Carolyn Green, 589382
      - Outline treatment, clean carbon, 1962 June; 589383; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 23)
      - Published play and rough outline of screenplay, with revisions, 1956 and n.d; 589384; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 24)
      - Screenplay: typed pages and handwritten notes, 1962 Sept-Nov; 589385; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Contracts, 1962; 589386; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Contracts, 1963; 589387; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1962-1963; 589388; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - United Artists invoices, 1963; 589389; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Clippings and publicity, 1962; 589390; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Harem by Abe Burrows, 589391
      - Script pages, draft, 1970-1972; 589392; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Story idea and handwritten notes, 1961-1963 and n.d; 589393; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Song lyrics, 1964 Apr-May; 589394; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Research for story, 1970; 589395; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Contracts, 1963-1964; 589396; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1970; 589397; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Clippings, 1964; 589398; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - The Man Who Came to Dinner, a play by Moss Hart and George Kaufman, proposed musical by Laurence Rosenthal with lyrics by James Lipton, 589399
      - Contracts: Chappell & Co. with Beresford Productions, 1964; 589400; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Contracts: dramatization agreement, 1964-1965; 589401; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - Contracts: minimum basic production, 1964; 589402; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Contracts: producing manager's, 1964; 589403; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - Contracts: United Artists, 1964; 589404; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, mostly legal, 1964-1966; 589405; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Blue Hour by Norman Krasna, 589406
      - Script, clean, 1968 Feb; 589407; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Script, with some handwritten revisions, 1967 Oct 8; 589408; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Script of Act II, mostly clean, 1968 Feb; 589409; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Scenes and revisions, some handwritten, various pagings, 1968 Feb; 589410; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Scenes and revisions, various pagings, 1968 Jan-Feb; 589411; 2 folders (Box 67, Folder 5-6)
      - Scenic plans by Oliver Smith, 1967; 589412; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Contracts: Director's agreement, 1968 Mar; 589413; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Contracts: Dramatists Guild Agreement, 1967 Oct; 589414; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Contracts: joint venture agreement, 1967 Oct-Nov; 589415; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Contracts with Norman Krasna, 1967 Sept-1968 June; 589416; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Legal correspondence, 1967 Oct-1968 June; 589417; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1968; 589418; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Tango Mogador, book by Abe Burrows, music by John Kander, lyrics by Fred Ebb, based on original screenplay by Rod Amateau and Harold Nebenzal, 589419
      - Script, mostly clean, with lyrics, n.d.; 589420; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
        One handwritten page inserted.
      - Screenplay, photocopied, "First Draft,", n.d.; 589421; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Draft of script with revisions, n.d.; 589422; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Draft of script with revisions, n.d.; 589423; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Notes and memos, 1971 Oct-1972 Jan; 589424; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Song lyrics, n.d.; 589425; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence on casting, 1972; 589426; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Contracts: director's agreement, 1971-1972; 589427; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Contracts: dramatization rights agreement, 1971; 589428; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Contracts: joint venture agreement, 1972; 589429; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Contracts: minimum basic production, 1971-1972; 589430; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - "Incidental documents,", 1971-1972; 589431; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Legal correspondence, 1971-1972; 589432; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 2)